todownload.com 2013-12-14

# weDownload

This website collects some Personal Data of its Users.

Information rights and express consent

According to what is set forth in current Privacy Policy, WeDownload Ltd., as owner of the Website, informs the User that files containing personal data from users and customers have been created by WeDownload, which accepts responsibility for the files, duly filed with the corresponding public entity.

WeDownload does not sell or rent its users' personal data to third parties with commercial purposes without the user' prior consent. However, WeDownload is enabled to disclose personal data in order to (i) fulfill a legal requirement, (ii) demand the fulfillment of our policies, (iii) answer claims regarding the breach or protection of any third party's rights or its property or security, in the event they are affected by advertisements or contents. WeDownload is enabled, as well, to share or transfer your personal information to:

Personal Data

The Personal Data and Browser Data (hereinafter collectively referred to as "Data"), automatically collected from this website (hereinafter the "Site"), by means of automated systems or freely entered by the User or the Interested Party, are collected for the purposes, and processed, as follows below.

Parties processing the data

**Owner of the Data Processing System**  
WeDownload Ltd. - Agiou Prokopiu Street, 13- 2406 Egkomi, Nicosia, Cyprus,  
contact at wedownload.com

Kinds of Data

The Data that may be collected by this Site are name, surname, address, phone number, email, fax, social security number, IP address and other Data relating to the User’s identity or technical access to the Site by the User. When Sensitive Personal Data are transferred (personal data revealing racial or ethnic, religious, philosophical or other beliefs, political opinions, membership of political parties, trade unions, associations or organizations of a religious, philosophical or political nature, and personal data disclosing information about health and sex life), it may be necessary to obtain consent in order to process them.

The Browser Data referring to the technical use of the Site must be collected, and transfer is not optional. The User may freely provide the remaining Data, including personal information, unless it is expressly indicated otherwise. Failure to process certain Data (e.g. contact details, or addresses, or data concerning behavior or user preferences, etc.) may make it impossible for the Site to provide its services.

If the User utilizes the Site to publish or otherwise share Personal Data with third parties, he or she assumes full responsibility: the User states possession of the right to communicate or disclose personal data to third parties, and that they have received prior information thereto, thus relieving the Site of all responsibility for their improper use following disclosure or dissemination.

Mode and place of processing of the information obtained

**Method of Processing**  
The Data Controller processes the Data of the Interested Parties and Users in a lawful and proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Data. Processing is carried out using computers and / or telematic means, with organizational methods and logics strictly related to the stated purposes. In addition to the owner, in some cases, access to the Data may be available to personnel involved in the organization of the Site (administrative, commercial, marketing, legal, system administrators) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Managers by the Owner of the Processing procedure. The updated list of Managers can be requested from the Owner by contacting the above address at any time.

**Place**  
The Data are processed at the headquarters of the Data Controller. Any processing of Data outside one of the EU Member States may require the consent of the User or the Interested Party.

**Time**  
The Data are kept for the time necessary to perform the service requested by the User, and the User can always ask for removal from the servers of the Site for legitimate reasons.

The use of the collected Data

the provision of the service or delivery of goods for sale purchased on the Site, and more generally, for administrative and accounting or technical purposes; 

  * The Provision Of The Service
  * a response to specific requests for information by the User;
  * a User update on new products or services provided by the Site or concerning particular business offers;
  * the User to be informed of any Site maintenance or inconvenience;
  * any commercial profiling of the User;
  * to display banners related to User interests (behavioral targeting / advertising);
  * defense by the Website Owner, in court or in the stages leading to possible legal action, against improper use of the same or related services by the User.

Some forms of processing (sending promotional information, commercial profiling, behavioral advertising, geolocation, etc.) may require the express consent of the User or the Interested Party. Specific information may be shown on the pages of the Site in connection with particular services or processing of Data provided by the User or by the Interested Party.

Services provided by this website

The use of Data for additional purposes by the Data Controller, or for services for which it is necessary to collaborate with third parties, listed below, may in some cases require the free and specific consent of the User or the Interested Party.

**Geolocation**  
This Website may collect, use, and share User location Data in order to provide location-based services. Most browsers and devices provide tools to opt out from this feature by default. If explicit authorization has been provided, this Site may track your location Data.

The personal data collected are: Geographic position.

Purpose of the information collected and Services utilized on the website

The purpose of the treatment of the personal information, the personal information collected and any suppliers of third party services involved are mentioned hereinafter.

**Google Adsense (Google)**  
The advertising services, provided by third parties, may allow the Website to use User’s Data for commercial communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on the Website based on Users’ interests.

Google Adsense is an advertising service that indexes, also through automatic means such as web spider or crawler, all or part of the Data of the User's Website. Google may also record through special "DoubleClick" cookies the User's behavior in his/her interaction with the User's Website. The cookies are used by Google and third parties to show different advertisements on the basis of User’s previous behavior.

The Users may decide to disable all the DoubleClick cookies by clicking on: [www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en)

Place of Data Processing: USA: [google.com/privacy/ads/](http://google.com/privacy/ads/)

The personal data collected are: Cookie and IP.

**Google Analytics (Google)**  
The analytics services contained in this section, provided by third parties, are used to track User behavior and, in case of profiling, they can require the User's express consent.

Google Analytics is a web analysis service supplied by Google, Inc. ("Google"), which uses "cookies" to collect Users’ Personal Data which are forwarded to, and deposited on, Google's servers in the United States. Google uses the Data collected to (i) track and examine the Website’s usage, (ii) prepare reports on the Website’s activities for the website managers and (iii) supply other optional services. Google may use the Data collected to carry out behavioral targeting of the Website’s Users. Google does not associate the user's IP address with any other information in Google's possession. Any refusal to utilize the cookies, by selecting the appropriate setup on your browser, may prevent the use of some functions of this Website.

Place of Data Processing: USA More information: [www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)

The personal data collected are: Cookie and IP.

**Information provided by minors**  
Users older than fourteen years old are able to register into the website without their parents' or tutors' prior consent.

In the event the User is a minor under fourteen, their parents' or tutors' prior consent is required for the handling of the minor's personal data. The minor will be never asked about other members of his/her family's professional or economic situation or their privacy.

The Rights of Interested Parties

Those persons to whom the Data refer, have the right, at any time, to obtain confirmation of the existence or otherwise of information by consulting the Data Controller, to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for their integration, cancellation, update or correction, their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Processor at the address cited in the "Data Controller" section.

**Right to Access, Correct and Cancel Data**  
The User is entitled to access this information, correct it if there are mistakes and cancel their WeDownload account.

Users can exercise these rights via the configuration menu in their personal profile, which they can access using their email address and password. If users experience problems while exercising their online rights or if they have doubts or questions related to our Personal Data Protection Policy they can contact us directly at:   
WeDownload Ltd.  
Agiou Prokopiu Street, 13- 2406 Egkomi, Nicosia, Cyprus,  
contact at wedownload.com

**Modification of the Data Protection Policy**  
WeDownload reserves the right to modify this policy to adapt it to future legislative or case law developments.

Definitions and legal references

**Personal information**  
Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.

**Browsing Details**  
Details collected automatically from the site, including the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the users who connect to the site, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file obtained in reply, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of provenance, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the visitor, the various time details per visit (for instance the time spent on each page) and the details about the path followed within the site with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, other parameters about the operating system and the user’s IT environment.

**User**  
Means the individual user of the Site’s services or products

**Interested Party**  
Indicates the subject to which the Personal Data refers, using the services or the products of the site.

**Data Processor**  
The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other organization, association or organization designated by the Data Controller for the Personal Data processing system.

**Data Controller**  
The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other organization, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Site.

**Legal information**  
This privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of cookies.

This privacy statement applies solely to the Site and is not meant to refer to other sites whose links are possibly contained therein.

_Last modified: 9th May 2012_
